

Bernard Muller

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER



Phone Number +27 78 213 3024

Website

https://bernardmuller.netlify.app/

Email Address

b.mullerjnr@gmail.com

Date Of Birth

23 May 1996

Linkedin bernardmuller

Github

bernardmuller

HOBBIES

Gaming

Programming

OBJECTIVE

Proactive professional with 2+ years of experience in a work environment and a proven knowledge of problem solving through design. Actively expanding my skillset and aiming to leverage my skills to successfully fill a Software Developer role.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance

Software Developer

(June 2020 - Present)

- Find and solve problems with software as a medium.
- Design and development of software with technologies like: Python, Node.js, MongoDB, React, HTML, CSS, JavaScript.

CNR Architects CC

(February 2019 - Present)

Architectural Technologist

- Generate detailed design documentation of luxury hotels in countries like Greece, Vietnam, Seychelles and Saudi Arabia that are designed by Denniston.
- Solve architectural problems with the use of visualizing, sketching and Autodesk Revit as the mediums.
- Maintain the basic Building Information Management (BIM) of the projects.

EDUCATION

Udemy

(December 2020 - April 2021)

The Web Developer Bootcamp 2021, by Colt Steele

University of Pretoria

(February 2015 - November 2018)

Bachelor's Degree Architecture

Montana Highschool

(January 2010 - November 2014)

National Senior Certificate

Top 50 academic student

SKILLS

Problem Solving

Good Communicator

Time Management

Quick Learner

PROJECTS

Personal Site

https://bernardmuller.netlify.app/

A 'business card' site I built for myself as a way to display my work and develop my ReactJS skills.

Timesheet Web

An automation app that helps an employee with the tracking of their work every day.

LANGUAGES

Afrikaans

English

Native

1st Additional